Oura KANO

Blockchain Fullstack Developer



% github.com/dev-tom-0108



Skills

Blockchain-Dapp,DAO

Solidity/Web3/React

Blockchain-Smart contract

Solidity

Web-Frontend

React/Redux/Redux-Saga/Redux-Thunk/Next/Material -UI/Vue.js / Vuex /Vuetify/Nuxt

Web-Backend

Node.js/Laravel/PHP/Mon goDB /MySQL

Mobile App/Game



Interests

Blockchain

Football

Art

About me

I am a passionate **Blockchain Fullstack Developer** particularly interested in newly-built all chains and high logic. I am an experienced IT professional with a unique combination of technical, consulting, and management skills. I am also a keen open-source developer—contributing several smaller utilities and libraries. I take great care in the experience, high logic, and architecture-especially fancy interface and code quality of the things I build.

I have studied abroad at Oxford University, so I can communicate in fluent English

Quality-oriented professional with 8+ years of experience and proven knowledge of IT strategy, programming, and web design.

Education

2010/07 - Bachelor of Science in Information Technology

2014/11 Kyoto University Kyoto, Japan

2014/12 - Bachelor of Science

2016/09 University of Oxford Oxford, United Kingdom

Work experience

2020/12 - Blockchain Fullstack Dev

2021/01 URL: https://shroomznft.io/

WORK: I designed this pages and I built this page by using Next.js and Web3. And I also coded the smart contract of minting NFTs-ERC721 by using Solidity.

2021/05 - Blockchain Fullstack Dev

2021/07 URL: https://foxfinance.io/Marketplace

WORK: I updated this page.

Before I worked, NFT cards were not allowed to change their properties once made. Then I add the functions to CHANGE the price and quantities and MAKE new card. Of course, I also rebuilt the website using **Nuxt.js** and **Web3** and the smart contract of marketplace by using

Solidity.

2021/08 - Frontend Dev

2021/10 URL: https://wooshi.world/

WORK: In this project, I modified some components of

this site.

This project was coded by **Shopify**. I worked on the internet to add **Web3** functions in this code and fixed 12 bugs

bugs.

2021/10 - Blockchain Fullstack Dev

2021/11 URL: https://boredzillaclub.com/

WORK: In this project, I also designed the page and built this site by using **Next.js** and **Web3**. Furthermore, I built smart contract of minting the NFTs-ERC721 by using **Solidity**.



United Kingdom Travel for language training

United States Travel for joining to companies and discuss Technical Problems

Employment

2014/12 -2018/02

Front End Developer

Wirecard Aschheim, Germany

- Requirements of the project include an implementation in Vue/Firebase with styling supported from Bootstrap and dynamic applications that can sort, filter data flawlessly using two-way data binding technique for overall performance.
- Encircle is a health insurance program financed and run jointly by the federal and state governments for low income people of all ages who do not have the money or insurance to pay for health care.
- The goal of the program is to provide medical and other health care services to eligible individuals so that they are able to remain as self-sufficient as possible.

2018/05 - 2020/02

Senior Full Stack Dev

Identiv Fremont, California, United States

- Used Hibernate as data mapping and persistence framework to implement data access abstraction.
- Fluency in HTML and CSS, and applied knowledge of client-side JavaScript, especially jQuery, React/Redux, Vue/Vuex, and other front-end libraries and frameworks.
- Worked with a React/AWS environment on a major enterprise product and it's already in production, Fiban.
- Supports and develops web application developers by providing advice, coaching and educational opportunities.
- Perform web development, template development, testing, debugging, integration, documentation and deployment in accordance with industry best practices.

2020/03 -2021/09

Blockchain Fullstack Dev

Simpplr Redwood City, California, United States

- Engaged with clients wanting to enter the blockchain space, especially in the Ethereum ecosystem.
- Designed and deployed smart contracts for tokens and ICOs including token vesting, refund vaults, and multisignature wallets.
- Implemented and deployed the graph for the staking contract tracking all events and allowing more advanced queries.
- Helped to integrate Ethereum and ER20 tokens into an exchange that is currently being built. It included address generation, token listing, and basic wallet operation related to ether and tokens using Web3.js.
- Researched the use of permissioned blocks and IPFS.
- Prototyped several optimizations including scheduling and specialized smart contracts.